Jigsaw : Hello , Mr. Hindle ,
or as they called you around the hospital- -
Zepp .
- ( electricity crackles ) - ( screaming )
GAME OVER !
( man panting )
( grunting )
( steam hissing )
- ( screaming ) - ( sizzling )
CHECK IT , MAN .
( crowd murmuring )
( gasps )
- ( metal clanking ) - ( grunting )
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS ?
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
I 'M FUCKING STUCK .
YEAH , ME TOO .
- WHAT THE FUCK ? ! - OH MY GOD .
SOMEBODY HELP US .
- HELLO . - COME ON , HELP US !
- ( gasping ) - OH MY GOD !
- OH , DINA . - BRAD .
- Dina : RYAN ? - BABY , ARE YOU OKAY ?
- GET ME OUT OF HERE ! - BABY .
HELP US . SOMEBODY HELP US !
HEY , CALL THE POLICE .
HEY , BREAK THE GLASS WITH YOUR CASE .
BREAK THE FUCKING GLASS ! DO IT .
STAY BACK ! STAY BACK !
DO IT ! ( grunting )
- Dina : GET ME OUT OF HERE . - BREAK IT !
Hello , Brad .
Hello , Ryan . I 'd like to play a game .
The same woman has played each of you for a fool ,
manipulating your love for her
and causing nothing but pain .
Her fun and games pushed you both to break the law
to fulfill her material needs .
She is toxic .
And today , all of your transgressions
will be made public .
HE 'S FUCKING LYING , BRAD .
Jigsaw : Now you must choose who will drop out of this triangle ,
for within 60 seconds one of you must die .
If you wish to save her ,
then the saws must be pushed
all the way to one side or the other ,
sparing her while proving for good
who is indeed the alpha male .
WHAT ARE YOU FUCKING STARING AT , YOU MOTHERFUCKERS ?
DO SOMETHING !
Jigsaw : Are you both strong enough
to walk away from what is destroying you ?
Or will you fight one more time
for the heart that binds ?
You have 60 seconds to decide .
Live or die . Make your choice .
- ( whirring ) - OH FUCK !
( screaming )
ONE OF YOU UNTIE ME , PLEASE !
( grunting )
( screams )
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING ?
IT 'S ME OR YOU ASSHOLE , AND IT SURE AS SHIT ISN 'T GONNA BE ME .
BRAD . BRAD .
- BRAD , I LOVE YOU . - I LOVE YOU TOO , BABY .
DO IT . YOU GOTTA DO IT .
- WHAT ? - YOU GOTTA KILL HIM , BRAD . DO IT !
- STUPID BITCH ! - DO IT .
DO IT . DO IT !
( screaming )
- ( sobbing ) - ( crowd gasps )
AW , FUCK !
- ( grunts ) - YOU LOVE HIM ?
NO NO .
- HUH ? YOU LOVE HIM MORE THAN ME ? - NO , I HAD TO SAY THAT .
I 'VE ALWAYS LOVED YOU .
YOU GOT TO DO IT FOR ME , PLEASE .
YOU GOT TO KILL HIM . KILL BRAD . DO IT !
- YOU LYING SLUT . - ( gasps )
- ( screaming ) - STOP !
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING ?
YOU DON 'T LOVE ANYBODY .
YOU 'RE A CHEAT AND A LIAR . FUCK YOU !
FUCK YOU !
BRAD . BRAD , LOOK AT ME .
IS THE CHICK THAT FUCKED ME IN YOUR BED TWO DAYS AGO WORTH ONE OF OUR LIVES ?
SHE 'S NOT WORTH IT , MAN . SHE 'S NOT WORTH IT .
- ( gasps ) - RIGHT ?
YEAH !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING , YOU FUCKING ASSHOLE ?
I THINK WE 'RE BREAKING UP WITH YOU , DINA .
NO ! NO , STOP ! ( screaming )
- ( gasping ) - ( Dina screaming )
STAND ASIDE ! MOVE IT !
( screaming )
PEOPLE , GET OUT OF THE WAY .
( clamoring )
SOMEBODY HELP HER .
( screaming )
( grunts )
- ( electricity sizzling ) - ( grunting )
( clicks )
- GAME OVER . - NO ! NO , YOU FUCKING BITCH !
NO !
( screaming )
( gasps )
( grunting )
( screaming )
( tears )
( panting )
TV Announcer : Tonight , a house of horrors has been discovered
at what used to be known as the Rowan Zoological Institute .
The body of Umbrella Health CEO
William Easton has been identified
as one of the several victims of this grizzly crime scene .
However , we have also been informed that there may be
as many as seven survivors from this deadly event .
Hopefully , the many questions of the local police ,
the FBI and the victims family members may be answered
by those seven civilians lucky enough
to walk away from this unprecedented display
of carnage with their lives .
We now go live to Tony Gabrielson
who is reporting from the scene .
Tony ...
( siren wailing )
- HEY , MAN . - HEY , WHAT 'S UP ?
( sighs ) WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE ?
THAT 'S JILL TUCK , JIGSAW 'S WIDOW .
- WHAT DOES SHE WANT ? - ALL SHE SAID WAS THAT SHE DIDN 'T TRUST THE FBI ...
- UH-HUH . - ... AND SHE DIDN 'T TRUST HOMICIDE .
- OH GOOD . - AND SHE JUST WANTS TO TALK TO YOU .
- WHY ME ? - I DON 'T KNOW .
ONLY YOU , THOUGH .
JEEZ . SHE LOOKS CRAZIER THAN A SACK FULL OF CATS .
ALL RIGHT , LET 'S GET THIS OVER WITH .
HEY . I PUT CREAM AND SUGAR IN IT .
- THANK YOU . - YOU 'RE WELCOME .
I 'M MATT GIBSON , INTERNAL AFFAIRS .
MY COLLEAGUE SAID THAT YOU WANTED TO SPEAK WITH ME .
YES .
BUT I NEED COMPLETE IMMUNITY .
WHY DO YOU WANT IMMUNITY , MS. TUCK ?
BECAUSE OF WHAT I KNOW .
WHICH IS WHAT ?
DO WE HAVE A DEAL ?
YOU 'VE GOT TO GIVE
BEFORE YOU CAN RECEIVE IN THIS HOUSE , JILL .
MY HUSBAND JOHN
- HAD AN ACCOMPLICE . - MMM .
A PERSON WHO ASSISTED HIM WITH ALMOST EVERY MURDER .
LOOK , DON 'T GET ME WRONG .
I 'M ALL EARS IF YOU 'VE GOT SOMETHING LEGIT THAT YOU WANT TO PUT ON THE TABLE .
THIS PERSON WILL GO ON KILLING
UNTIL HE 'S STOPPED .
YOU KNOW HIM , AND HE DEFINITELY KNOWS YOU .
IS THAT RIGHT ?
HE 'S DETECTIVE MARK HOFFMAN .
ARE YOU WILLING TO SIGN A SWORN AFFIDAVIT ?
YES .
YOU SWEAR TO BE TOTALLY OPEN ?
YOU TELL ME EVERYTHING , NO MATTER HOW PERSONAL OR PRIVATE ?
YES .
I 'LL GIVE YOU EVIDENCE , WHATEVER YOU WANT .
AS LONG AS I HAVE YOUR PROTECTION
AND COMPLETE IMMUNITY .
DO WE HAVE A DEAL ?
OH YEAH , WE HAVE A DEAL .
Woman : WELCOME BACK !
WE 'RE LIVE WITH BOBBY DAGEN WHOSE NATIONAL TOUR
" S.U.R.V.I.V.E : MY STORY OF OVERCOMING JIGSAW "
ROLLS INTO TOWN THIS WEEKEND .
YOU 'RE QUITE THE NATIONAL PHENOMENON THESE DAYS , AREN 'T YOU ?
WELL , THANK YOU , MA 'AM .
IT 'S QUITE FLATTERING HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE RESPONDED TO MY STORY .
AND IF I CAN HELP A FEW PEOPLE ALONG THE WAY ,
THEN I 'M PLEASED .
NOW YOU SURVIVED A TRAP CREATED
BY THE INFAMOUS JIGSAW KILLER , CORRECT ?
YES MA 'AM .
WELL , EVERYONE MUST ASK YOU THIS QUESTION :
WHAT WAS THAT LIKE ?
LIFE CHANGING .
IT WAS SOMETHING I NEVER ANTICIPATED AND QUITE HONESTLY ,
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD HAVE KILLED ME .
TELL ME MORE . TELL ME ABOUT THE ACTUAL EXPERIENCE .
I ACTUALLY HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF HOW I GOT THERE .
I JUST REMEMBER THE FEELING
OF WAKING UP TRAPPED .
AND I HAD TO INSERT TWO HOOKS
INTO MY PECTORAL MUSCLES
AND HOIST MYSELF UP TO A PLATFORM .
- YOU PUT THE HOOKS IN YOURSELF ? - I DID .
I PRETTY MUCH REALIZED THAT I COULDN 'T HOLD ON MUCH LONGER
AND I HAD TO ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT I WAS GOING TO DIE .
AND THEN I SAW SOMETHING ,
AND WHAT I SAW WAS MY LIFE .
IT WAS A TRAGEDY .
I ACHIEVED NOTHING .
AND RIGHT THEN ,
SOMETHING INSIDE ME STARTED TO GROW .
SOMETHING FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY SOUL .
AND I JUST- - I DECIDED TO LIVE .
I FOUND A STRENGTH THAT I THOUGHT HAD LONG SINCE EXPIRED .
AND I JUST YANKED AND I YANKED .
AND WHEN I GOT TO THE TOP , I JUST RIPPED THE HOOKS OUT OF MY CHEST .
THERE WAS BLOOD EVERYWHERE AND I JUST SCREAMED .
I JUST SAT THERE AND SCREAMED .
BECAUSE I HADN 'T JUST SURVIVED .
I WAS REBORN .
THIS WAS MY LIFE .
WOW !
BOBBY DAGEN , EVERYONE .
BOBBY 'S LIFE-CHANGING EXPERIENCE COMES TO THE ...
THIS IS THE MOMENT .
- WHERE 'S THE BIG KISS ? - I DON 'T KNOW .
TICKETS ARE STILL AVAILABLE .
Director : AND WE 'RE OUT , FOLKS .
THAT 'S NOT THE WAY IT 'S SUPPOSED TO BE .
NO , WE REHEARSED IT DIFFERENTLY .
IT 'S OKAY . NICE WORK , BOBBY .
HEY , LADIES , CAN YOU EXCUSE US FOR A MINUTE ?
WHERE WAS THE BIG FINISH , BOBBY , HMM ?
YOU TELL YOUR STORY , YOU THANK YOUR PRETTY WIFE .
YOU BRING HER OUT FOR A BIG HUG AND KISS .
I JUST DIDN 'T WANT TO PUSH IT , ALL RIGHT ?
OKAY , BUT THAT 'S THE HEART OF THE STORY .
SHE WAS THERE FOR YOUR WHOLE RECOVERY .
AND WITHOUT THE ACKNOWLEDGMENT , WITHOUT THE KISS ,
THE AUDIENCE ISN 'T GONNA HAVE ANY KIND OF EMOTIONAL CONNECTION .
I DISAGREE . TOO MUCH EMOTION AND IT 'S GONNA FEEL LIKE PANDERING .
OKAY , WHY DON 'T YOU LET ME DO THE PUBLIC RELATIONS
AND YOU DO THE LEGAL PAPERWORK , OKAY ?
OKAY , I GET IT , SUZANNE , ALL RIGHT ? IT 'S MY FAULT .
IT WASN 'T YOUR FAULT , BOBBY .
YOU WERE FINE . JUST REMEMBER YOUR BULLET POINTS NEXT TIME .
- I WILL . - THESE INTERVIEWS ARE IMPORTANT .
Man : NINA , RELAX .
DON 'T WORRY ABOUT THEM . YOU WERE GREAT .
- YEAH ? - YOUR STORY 'S REAL AND PEOPLE FEEL THAT .
I KNOW THAT YOU GET OVERWHELMED AT TIMES ,
BUT WE HAVE TO KEEP MOVING FORWARD , BOBBY .
YOU WERE MEANT TO DO THIS .
I KNOW . I KNOW , BABY .
- BOBBY . - YEAH ?
WE GOT THE JIGSAW SURVIVOR GROUP TOMORROW .
30 MINUTES OF FACE TIME WITH OTHER SURVIVORS .
YEAH , SOUNDS GOOD .
- NOTHING MORE EXCITING THAN THAT . - NO , NOT MUCH .
LET 'S GO .
( police radio chatter )
( shrieks )
( mechanical whirring )
( gasps ) OH GOD !
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE ONLY THING WRONG WITH KILLING YOU , JILL ?
I CAN ONLY DO IT ONCE .
- ( clicking ) - ( whimpering )
OH MY GOD ! NO !
NO !
( gasps )
( grunts )
HELP ME ! HELP ME !
HELP ! FUCK !
Jigsaw : Hello , Evan .
I want to play a game .
The situation you find yourself in is of your own doing .
You , your girlfriend and your friends
are all racists .
EVAN , YOU FUCK . YOU GET ME OUT OF HERE !
You have intimidated others ...
- WHAT THE FUCK ? - ... based on their physical differences .
- But today it is you who will run scared . - WHAT THE FUCK , MAN ?
Your pathetic friends follow your every word , Evan .
Therefore , you will be the only one capable
of saving them and yourself .
In 30 seconds , the jacks holding up this car will fall ...
( wailing )
... setting off a deadly chain of events .
In order to stop this from happening ,
you must tear yourself away
from the seat to which you are glued .
Then you must pull the red lever before you .
But no act comes without a sacrifice .
- You 've judged others by the color of their skin ... - FUCK !
... and today , Evan , you will learn
that we are all the same color on the inside .
Live or die , Evan ,
the choice is yours .
- ( screaming ) - ( engine starts )
NO !
( screaming )
( engine revving )
- Woman : EVAN , HELP ! - I CAN 'T .
DO IT . JUST DO IT . FUCKING DO IT !
JUST FUCKING DO IT ?
DO IT ! DO IT , MAN !
HERE I GO ! ( screaming )
EVAN ! BABY , GET ME OUT OF HERE !
SHIT ! FUCK !
HERE I COME !
HERE I COME ! FUCK ME !
HELP ME , PLEASE .
- GOD ! - DO IT ! FUCKING DO IT !
- GOD ! - DO IT !
- EVAN ! - YOU GOT US INTO THIS .
GET US THE FUCK OUT !
- ( screaming ) - DO IT !
YOU 'RE A FUCKING PUSSY !
( all screaming )
- ( beeping ) - SHIT .
( woman sobbing ) EVERY NIGHT ...
I KEEP THINKING THAT THINGS WILL GET BETTER
THE NEXT MORNING WHEN I WAKE UP .
BUT IT ISN 'T .
EVERYTHING I DO ,
EVERYTHING I SEE ,
I 'M SURROUNDED BY THESE
TINY TRIGGERS .
THEY 'RE EVERYWHERE ,
AND THEY REMIND ME OF WHAT I WENT THROUGH ,
WHAT JIGSAW DID TO ME . ( crying )
SIDNEY , GO ON , PLEASE .
YOU 'RE- - YOU 'RE IN A SAFE PLACE NOW .
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED NEXT .
- ALEX ! STOP , PLEASE ! STOP IT ! - ( grunting )
PLEASE ! ALEX !
- ( Alex screams ) - ( blades whirring )
( screaming )
SIDNEY , LOOK AT ME .
YOU MADE A DECISION .
HOW DID THAT MAKE YOU FEEL ?
FREE .
HE WAS ABUSIVE .
I TRIED TO STOP IT BEFORE ,
BUT IT WASN 'T UNTIL THAT MOMENT
THAT I REALLY DID SOMETHING .
IT WAS HIM OR ME , AND I CHOSE TO LIVE .
IT WAS THE BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME .
THAT 'S A BUNCH OF BULLSHIT .
HE HAD TO DIE FOR YOU TO LEAVE HIM ?
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT THE BEST THING THAT HAPPENED TO ME
AFTER HAVING TO CUT OFF MY OWN ARM ?
IT 'S HANDICAPPED PARKING
AT THE DAMN MALL .
WHAT THE HELL IS A CAMERA HERE FOR ANYWAY ?
I AM SIMPLY HERE TO ILLUSTRATE THE FACT THAT A TRAUMATIC EXPERIENCE ,
SUCH AS THE KIND THAT EACH ONE OF US HAVE BEEN FORCED TO ENDURE ,
CAN HAVE A POSITIVE OUTCOME . THAT 'S ALL .
YEAH ? LIKE WHAT ?
A NEW PERSPECTIVE ON LIFE . WHOA WHOA WHOA , WAIT .
I KNOW .
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU 'RE NOT AT THAT PLACE YET .
I UNDERSTAND THAT AND I RESPECT THAT .
BUT IF YOU LOOK AROUND AT ALL THESE PEOPLE
TAKING THEIR LIVES FOR GRANTED ,
EVENTUALLY THEY ALL FOUND SOMETHING POSITIVE
FROM THEIR EXPERIENCE .
WE SHOULD NEVER BE ASHAMED OF WHAT WE 'VE GONE THROUGH .
BECAUSE WE ARE GOOD AND WE ARE STRONG !
YOU KNOW WHAT ?
I 'D LIKE EVERYBODY TO HAVE A LOOK AT SOMETHING RIGHT HERE .
THESE ARE MY SCARS .
BECAUSE OUR MINDS WILL HEAL ,
BUT THESE SCARS WILL NEVER GO AWAY .
THESE SCARS SHOULD NOT BE A SYMBOL OF SHAME .
THEY SHOULD BE WORN AS A BADGE OF COURAGE .
YOU KNOW , EARLIER ,
I SPOKE
OF VALUING YOUR LOVED ONES .
BUT TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST ,
IT 'S SOMETHING THAT I NEVER DID PRIOR TO MY ORDEAL .
BUT SINCE THEN ,
I HAVE FOUND SOMEONE
WHO HAS TRULY BECOME MY ROCK .
JOYCE , IF YOU COULD- -
PLEASE .
IT 'S MY LOVELY WIFE JOYCE .
- I LOVE YOU . - I LOVE YOU TOO , BABY .
BRAVO . HMM .
TO BE ABLE TO SUSTAIN SUCH A TRAUMATIC EXPERIENCE
AND YET FIND THE POSITIVE
IN THAT GRIZZLY ACT ,
IT 'S A REMARKABLE FEAT INDEED .
REMARKABLE ,
IF NOT A LITTLE PERVERSE .
I 'M SURE I SPEAK FOR EVERYONE HERE WHEN I SAY
HOW GRATEFUL WE ARE
TO BE PART OF YOUR
PROMOTIONAL DVD .
I APPRECIATE IT . THANK YOU . IT 'S- -
- I CAN TAKE THAT , SIR . - THANK YOU VERY MUCH .
JOYCE , CAN I BORROW HIM FOR A SEC ?
- SURE . I 'LL BE IN THE CAR , OKAY ? - TWO MINUTES BEHIND YOU .
- GREAT . - YOU 'LL SEE HER TO THE CAR , PLEASE ?
- OF COURSE . - THANK YOU .
WHAT 'S UP ?
SO WHAT 'S WITH THE CREEPY GUY WITH THE CANE ? SOMEONE I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT ?
NO NO NO . HE 'S BEEN AT THESE MEETINGS LONGER THAN I HAVE .
HE 'S FINE .
ALL RIGHT .
LISTEN , GET BACK TO THE HOTEL AND GET SOME REST , ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH . EVERYTHING 'S FINE .
GREAT WORK TONIGHT , BOBBY .
- THANK YOU . - YOU 'RE THE MAN .
JOYCE ? ( gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM ?
THEY ALWAYS TELL YOU NOT TO SMOKE AT THE GAS STATION .
THIS SHOULD WRAP UP THE WEEK FOR YOU .
GREAT .
( cell phone rings )
WHAT 'S UP , MAN ?
I 'M AT A JUNKYARD ON 58th .
- WHY ? - Call came in about a car crash .
Car crash ? Why are you there ?
IT 'S NOT JUST A CAR CRASH . IT 'S A TRAP .
HOW MANY BODIES ?
Enough pieces to make four .
OKAY , GET EVERYONE AWAY FROM THAT CRIME SCENE TILL I GET THERE .
- Even Homicide , you got it ? - YEAH .
ALL RIGHT , I 'M ON THE WAY .
( Jigsaw distorted ) Hello , Evan .
I want to play a game .
The situation you find yourself in is of your own doing .
You , your girlfriend and your friends
are all racists .
You have intimidated others
based on their physical differences ...
( distortion )
- ( police radio chatter ) - ( sirens wailing )
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
WHY ?
WHY THIS DISPLAY ?
WHY THEM ? WHY NOW ?
YOU KNOW HE LIKES TO PUT ON A SHOW .
WELL , IT 'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING ELSE .
BAG THE OTHER BODIES . GET THEM BACK TO THE CORONER 'S OFFICE RIGHT AWAY .
WE 'LL NEED THEM CHECKED FOR ANYTHING RESEMBLING A CLUE- -
TATTOOS , PIERCINGS , SKIN CUTTINGS .
IF THAT MAN HAS A CAVITY IN HIS TOOTH , I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT .
- YES SIR . - ALL RIGHT .
- GIBSON . - YEAH ?
HOFFMAN WAS EXPECTING YOU .
Man : PUT ON YOUR GLOVES .
( sniffs ) GOD DAMN .
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT ? PLEASE GET FORENSICS IN HERE .
TELL THEM TO HAUL ASS .
THIS NEEDS TO BE DUSTED FOR PRINTS .
- ALL RIGHT . - OKAY .
( grunts )
( groans )
HELP !
( static hisses )
Hello , Bobby .
I want to play a game .
You have amassed wealth ,
fame and notoriety
based upon your story of survival .
Many have aided in your cause ,
but few know the truth .
You are a liar .
You and I both know you have never been in a trap ,
nor have you ever been tested .
Today these lies will come full circle
and you will learn
if you truly have what it takes
to call yourself a survivor .
The cage you find yourself in
will symbolize your rebirth .
JOYCE ? NO !
JOYCE ! NO !
PLEASE , NO .
Within the next 60 minutes ,
you must stay upon the path of learning
and traverse a series of obstacles
to obtain access to your wife ,
who you also have deceived .
If you fail to reach her before the clock runs out ,
- she will die . - NO .
Live or die , Bobby ? Make your choice .
( mechanical whirring )
( screams )
( grunting )
BOBBY !
HELP !
LET ME OUT !
BOBBY . BOBBY !
WHAT 'S GOING ON ? WHAT 'S GOING ON ?
TV Announcer : Another Jigsaw survivor has come forward .
As the city stays crippled in fear from the Jigsaw killings ,
chilling new words from the latest survivor provide a reminder
of the physical and mental toll
these deadly games can take .
This horrible event
was happening to me ,
and in that moment ,
that moment that this thing
threatened to take everything away ,
even the pain ...
I realized what I still had left to give .
And I didn 't want to let that go .
It gave me light .
That pure moment
of absolute horror gave me light .
And as wrong as this may seem ,
I 'm better for enduring it .
I 'm stronger .
And I must admit , I 'm grateful for it .
I 'm grateful it happened to me .
And I wish the same for everyone like me .
Announcer : Joan is but one of a growing number of citizens ...
IF SOMETHING LIKE THAT DOESN 'T GET YOU
TO CHANGE YOUR PERSPECTIVE ON LIFE ,
I DON 'T KNOW WHAT WILL .
YEAH .
( scoffs )
AND IF THOSE PEOPLE WEREN 'T SO FUCKED UP AFTER THEIR GAMES ,
THEY 'D MAKE A MINT SELLING THEIR STORIES .
OH SHIT .
SHIT .
WELL , THAT 'S A REAL CLEVER DESIGN .
YOURS OR YOUR HUSBAND 'S ?
- EVERYTHING WAS HIM . - RIGHT . WELL , HERE 'S MY PROBLEM .
THAT WAS LEFT FOR ME
AND YOUR FINGERPRINTS WERE ALL OVER IT .
WHEN YOU TOLD ME HOFFMAN HAD IT IN FOR YOU ,
YOU DIDN 'T MENTION THAT IT WAS BECAUSE YOU TRIED TO KILL HIM .
THERE 'S A NEW GAME GOING ON .
DOES THAT SURPRISE YOU ?
NO .
NO ? NO ?
YOU 'RE CRAZY , YOU KNOW THAT ?
I KNEW YOU WERE CRAZY THE MINUTE I LAID EYES ON YOU .
CRAZY .
OKAY , THIS IS WHAT WE 'RE GONNA DO , CRAZY .
TILL I CATCH MARK HOFFMAN ,
THIS IS YOUR NEW HOME . GET COMFY .
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK HE CAN 'T FIND ME HERE ?
JILL , IT 'S A SAFE HOUSE . SAFE HOUSE .
SAFE HOUSE . YOU GET IT ?
GIBSON , THIS WAS SENT HERE
ADDRESSED TO JILL . HOFFMAN KNOWS OUR LOCATION .
GOD DAMN IT . GOD DAMN IT !
- ( cell phone rings ) - WHAT ?
WE JUST HAD A SMALL EXPLOSION HERE IN A CAR AT THE CRIME SCENE .
- Okay , is anyone hurt ? - OH SHIT !
- ROGERS ? ROGERS , YOU OKAY ? - YEAH .
GET OUT OF THERE . YOU GET THE BOMB SQUAD TO SWEEP THE YARD .
Don 't touch anything else until it 's clean .
- GOT IT . - All right .
PLAY IT .
Hello , Gibson .
Been a long time .
What I want is simple . Give me Jill Tuck .
You 're protecting her despite the fact
that she had direct knowledge throughout ,
which makes her complicit in every death .
I 'll make you a deal .
Give her to me .
The game stops and no one else dies .
If not ,
everyone dies and you 'll be to blame .
Make your choice .
The clock 's ticking .
LET 'S GET HER DOWN TO THE HOLDING CELL AT THE STATION .
LOCK IT DOWN . NO ONE GETS IN WITHOUT MY AUTHORITY .
GOT IT .
( woman whimpering ) OH MY GOD .
OH GOD ! NO ! PLEASE ! ( screaming )
NO ! PLEASE !
PLEASE , NO ! GOD DAMN IT !
BOBBY . BOBBY , HELP ME !
YOU 'VE GOT TO GET ME OUT OF HERE .
I CAN 'T MOVE , BOBBY .
- PLEASE , HELP ME ! - OKAY OKAY OKAY . JUST RELAX .
OW .
OW !
HELP ME ! DO SOMETHING !
DON 'T LEAVE ME .
Jigsaw : Hello , Bobby .
Before you is one of your trusted colleagues .
She has been your publicist for years ,
knowing your lies ,
but choosing to speak no evil .
She has been richly rewarded for her words ,
but today she will be rewarded for her silence .
In the X-ray , you will see a key ,
the key to Nina 's survival ,
which will shut off her device .
But there 's a catch .
You have one minute to pull the fish hook from her stomach
and unlock her device
or else the four spikes will penetrate her throat ,
- silencing Nina forever . - FUCK !
Remember , the spikes will also advance
each time the decibel level in this room
rises above a whisper ,
killing her even sooner .
- Will Nina live or die , Bobby ? - ( screaming )
The choice is yours .
HELP ME . HELP !
- NO ! - ( muffled screaming )
( ticking )
JUST SHUT UP .
STAY WITH ME , OKAY ?
DO IT . ( grunting )
( screaming )
NO . NO . NO .
OKAY , STAY WITH ME . STAY WITH ME .
IT 'S GONNA BE OKAY . LOOK AT ME . LOOK AT ME .
( whimpers )
( screams )
NO ! NINA , QUIET .
PLEASE PLEASE , FOR ME . JUST SHUT THE FUCK UP .
I 'M GONNA GET THIS OUT .
( ticking )
( gagging )
- ( screams ) - NO ! NO !
JUST DO IT , BOBBY .
JUST FUCKING DO IT .
( coughs )
( screaming )
BOBBY !
NO !
WHY WOULDN 'T YOU JUST SHUT THE FUCK UP ? !
YOU JUST NEEDED TO SHUT UP !
Joyce : NO ! OH MY GOD !
NO ! HELP !
( shrieks )
HELP ! HELP !
HERE YOU ARE , MA 'AM . TAKE CARE .
MA 'AM , YOUR NAME ?
SARA- - WITHOUT AN H.
I JUST WANT TO SAY I LOVE YOUR BOOK SO MUCH .
I JUST FELT LIKE I COULD FEEL EVERYTHING THAT YOU WENT THROUGH .
I FEEL LIKE IT CHANGED MY LIFE .
I APPRECIATE THAT , MA 'AM .
I REALLY DO . THANK YOU .
THANK YOU .
YOUR NAME , SIR ?
JOHN .
WITH AN H ,
WITHOUT AN H , IT DOESN 'T MATTER .
WE 'LL GO WITH JOHN WITH AN H THIS TIME .
YOU GOT QUITE AN ARMY WORKING FOR YOU HERE , DON 'T YOU ?
MUST BE SPREADING A PRETTY GOOD WORD .
WELL , WE TRY TO REACH AS MANY PEOPLE AS POSSIBLE , YOU KNOW ?
YOU DON 'T SEE ANYTHING WRONG WITH THAT ?
( laughs ) NO . NO SIR , I DON 'T .
YOU KNOW ,
HISTORY IS A PASSION FOR ME .
AND IN ANCIENT EGYPT IF YOU WERE SPEAKING UNDER OATH ,
YOU WERE REQUIRED TO SAY ,
" IF I 'M LYING ,
TAKE ME TO THE QUARRIES . "
THAT MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU ?
NO SIR . NO SIR , IT DOESN 'T .
WELL , I 'LL TELL YOU WHAT IT MEANS .
IT MEANS IF YOU KNOWINGLY LIED
ON THE PUBLIC RECORD
THAT YOU WERE SUBJECT TO A PERIOD OF ENSLAVEMENT .
WHAT ARE YOU IMPLYING HERE , SIR ?
I 'M NOT IMPLYING ANYTHING .
MOVE ALONG , BUDDY . HE SIGNED YOUR BOOK .
THANKS FOR THE SIGNATURE .
NICE PICTURE , BUT I DON 'T NEED IT .
WE 'VE MET .
ADAM , GIBSON SAYS HE WANTS YOU ON THESE RIGHT AWAY .
THEY 'RE FROM THE JUNKYARD .
Hoffman : Make your choice .
- The clock 's ticking . - ( beeps )
- SEE THAT ? - YEAH .
I KNOW THAT FROM SOMEWHERE .
Woman : HEY , I 'VE GOT SOMETHING OVER HERE .
WE MIGHT KNOW WHO 'S IN THE GAME .
THIS WAS JUST SENT TO US . IT WAS TAKEN FROM A SECURITY CAMERA DOWNTOWN .
THE GUY 'S NAME IS BOBBY DAGEN .
- FAMILIAR ? - NO .
HE 'S A JIGSAW SURVIVOR WHO 'S MILKING IT ON TALK SHOWS .
HIS WIFE AND HANDLERS ARE ALSO MISSING .
( woman whimpering )
- JOYCE ? - ( screaming )
WHO IS IT ? WHO 'S THERE ?
- SUZANNE . - WHO IS THAT ?
FOR FUCK 'S SAKE , BOBBY . BOBBY .
BOBBY , GET ME OUT OF HERE . BOBBY , HELP ME .
- IS CALE HERE ? - WHO THE FUCK KNOWS ?
GET THIS OFF OF ME , BOBBY ! GET THIS OFF OF ME !
( screaming )
Hello , Bobby . That feeling running
through your body is fear- -
the fear of not knowing
if you have what it takes to survive .
Before you is your lawyer
who swore an oath of ethics ,
but chose to see no evil
in order to benefit herself .
Once her device begins to rotate ,
it will pierce her eyes and mouth if you don 't delay
its movement for at least 30 seconds .
To do this ,
you must step into the other machine
and lift the bars to the highest position long enough
to close the circuit , slowing down her device .
If you do nothing , she will wind to her death
before the clock runs out .
Do you have what it takes to help her ?
Make your choice .
BOBBY , PLEASE ! BOBBY , PLEASE GET ME OUT !
GET ME THE FUCK- - ( screaming )
- ( trap whirring ) - OH GOD !
NO NO ! BOBBY , PLEASE !
PLEASE , HELP ME !
OH GOD ! OH FUCK !
PLEASE HURRY ! HURRY !
COME ON , BOBBY , PLEASE !
HURRY ! COME ON ! BOBBY , COME ON !
HURRY ! PLEASE !
PLEASE , HURRY !
( grunting )
BOBBY , PLEASE , HURRY ! HURRY !
( buzzer sounds )
- ( trap powers down ) - Bobby : YEAH !
COME ON !
BOBBY , NO .
( groaning )
( buzzer sounds )
NO ! OH GOD , NO !
NO ! BOBBY !
PLEASE , NO ! BOBBY , NO !
COME ON , BOBBY . PLEASE ! GET ME OUT OF HERE !
COME ON !
BOBBY , PLEASE !
NO ! OH GOD .
OH MY GOD . BOBBY , STAY THERE .
- ( buzzer sounds ) - BOBBY , PLEASE , NO !
NO ! NO !
( grunting )
( screaming )
NO !
PLEASE PLEASE !
NO ! OH GOD ! ( screaming )
( buzzer sounds )
- ( beeps ) - ( Bobby whimpering )
- OH MY GOD . - ( metal clangs )
NO . NO .
HELP !
DO YOU KNOW THIS GUY ?
I 'VE SEEN HIM ON TV , BUT I DON 'T KNOW HIM .
- DID YOUR HUSBAND ? - I DON 'T KNOW .
YOU SURE YOU DON 'T KNOW HIM ?
YEAH , I 'M SURE .
ALL RIGHT THEN .
LOCK IT UP .
HOFFMAN JUST SENT AN EMAIL WITH AN MPEG ATTACHMENT .
I 'M JUST SEARCHING THE I.P. ADDRESS .
CAN YOU FIND OUT WHERE IT CAME FROM ?
IT DEPENDS ON HOW MANY PROXY SERVERS HE FILTERED IT THROUGH ,
BUT IT WAS TIME-DELAYED , SO IT 'LL LEAVE FINGERPRINTS .
- PLAY IT . - ( beeps )
Hello , Gibson .
Once again , we 're at a moral crossroad .
I don 't blame you for not giving me Jill Tuck .
But you shouldn 't let an old grudge cloud your judgment .
Look to where you 're being led .
Look beyond the crossroad
to the clear dawn .
Do you see it ?
I GET IT . LET 'S GO .
JOYCE ?
( grunts )
( panting )
- CALE ? - BOBBY ? BOBBY ?
CALE , I CAN SEE YOU , OKAY ?
- CALE , DON 'T MOVE . - BOBBY , WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU ?
- YOU GOT TO HELP ME , BOBBY . - DO YOU KNOW WHERE JOYCE IS ?
WHAT THE FUCK ? I CAN 'T SEE , MAN .
HOW THE FUCK WOULD I KNOW WHERE JOYCE IS ?
I 'M ABOUT TO LOSE MY SHIT !
DO I KNOW WHERE JOYCE IS ? I 'M FUCKING BLIND , MAN .
OKAY , CALE . CALE , DO NOT MOVE .
I GOT THIS THING AROUND MY FUCKING NECK . I CAN 'T FUCKING BREATHE .
DON 'T FUCKING MOVE . WE 'RE NOT ON THE GROUND FLOOR .
A LOT OF THIS FLOOR IS MISSING . JUST DON 'T MOVE , OKAY ?
FUCK . YOU GOTTA HELP ME .
GET ME FUCKING DOWN , BOBBY ! FUCK ! OH , FUCK ME !
CALE , THERE 'S A TAPE .
- WHAT FUCKING TAPE ? - THERE 'S A TAPE .
SHUT UP . I 'M GONNA PLAY THE TAPE .
( clicks )
Jigsaw : Hello , Bobby .
Across from you is your closest friend .
He knows all your sins ,
yet he acts as though he hears no evil .
Today , what he hears
will be the difference between life and death .
Bobby , you must help Cale walk over the planks
and get as close to you as possible .
Find your own way across the beams to the key .
You must get it to him over the last span between you .
If the noose around Cale 's neck
is not removed within 60 seconds ,
a winch will be engaged
and your secret will be left hanging .
Does Cale live or die , Bobby ?
The choice is yours .
BOBBY ! OH GOD .
CALE . CALE , LISTEN TO ME .
LISTEN TO ME . SHUT THE FUCK UP AND YOU LISTEN TO ME FOR ONCE .
LISTEN , I 'M GONNA WALK YOU THROUGH THIS , OKAY , BUDDY ?
I 'M BLIND . YOU FUCKING COME TO ME .
I 'M GONNA TRY TO GET AS CLOSE TO YOU AS I CAN , BUDDY .
I 'M FUCKING LISTENING TO YOU . TALK ME FUCKING THROUGH THIS .
I WANT YOU TO SHUFFLE TO YOUR RIGHT .
JUST SHUFFLE EXACTLY TO YOUR RIGHT .
YOU 'RE GONNA FEEL A PLANK AT YOUR FOOT . YES YES .
YES YES , PERFECT . I NEED YOU TO HEAD OUT ON THAT PLANK .
- OH FUCK . - YES .
OKAY , I GOT IT . I GOT IT . I GOT IT !
OH , FUCK THIS .
OKAY , CALE , I 'M ON THE WAY .
OH FUCK . OH FUCK . OKAY , ALL RIGHT .
NOW THERE 'S GONNA BE A PLANK IN FRONT OF YOU .
- OKAY . - YOU 'RE GONNA GO ABOUT 10 ° TO YOUR RIGHT .
I GOT IT . I GOT IT .
- COME ON , KEEP FUCKING TALKING TO ME . - OKAY , CALE .
- FEEL WHERE THE PLANK- - - I GOT IT .
OKAY .
OH GOD ! WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT , MAN ?
IT 'S OKAY , CALE . IT WAS A BOTTLE . IT WAS A BOTTLE .
- WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT ? - IT 'S OKAY . IT WAS A BOTTLE .
- YOU 'RE GONNA BE FINE . - OKAY .
- OH FUCK . OKAY . - YOU GOT IT , BUDDY .
YOU GOT IT . NOW YOU 'RE GONNA FEEL A SECOND PLANK .
- YOU 'LL FEEL IT WITH YOUR FOOT . - I GOT IT .
FEEL IT WITH YOUR FOOT .
GET ME OUT OF THIS FUCKING THING , BOBBY .
STEP UP ONTO THE PLANK .
OH FUCK . OH GOD .
RELAX . YOU 'RE OKAY .
NO ! NO !
CALE , HANG ON . CALE .
OH FUCK . OH FUCK .
( whimpering )
BOBBY . BOBBY .
( grunts )
I GOT THE KEY . CALE , I 'M GONNA THROW YOU THE KEY .
CUP YOUR HANDS CLOSER TO YOUR CHEST !
I 'M GONNA THROW IT ON THREE , ALL RIGHT ?
ONE ...
TWO ...
THREE .
( clangs )
NO .
- ( timer beeping ) - OH FUCK ME .
- ( buzzer sounds ) - ( screaming )
NO ! GOD DAMN IT , NO !
( gagging )
CALE !
Joyce : NO . CALE .
( crying )
NO .
- THERE 'S NOTHING HERE . - YES THERE IS .
RIGHT THERE .
WHY WOULD HE WANT US TO COME HERE ?
FOR ME TO REMEMBER .
THIS IS WHERE HE SAVED MY LIFE .
WHEN I WAS IN UNIFORM
I RESPONDED TO A DISTRESS CALL HERE
BACK WHEN THIS PLACE WAS A FLOPHOUSE FOR JUNKIES AND HOMELESS PEOPLE .
( grunting )
FREEZE ! DON 'T YOU FUCKING MOVE .
DROP THE GUN .
( gunshots )
HE DIDN 'T KNOW WHAT HIT HIM .
YEAH , HE ASSAULTED ME ,
BUT IT SHOULDN 'T HAVE BEEN A DEATH SENTENCE .
NEXT TIME YOU SHOOT FIRST .
Gibson : I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO REPORT HOFFMAN FOR BRUTALITY .
YOU OWE ME .
Rogers : WHAT HAPPENED ?
HE GOT A PROMOTION IS WHAT HAPPENED .
AND I GOT PUT ON AN ISLAND .
A YEAR LATER , I TRANSFERRED TO I.A. , BUSTED THREE OF HIS GUYS .
HE SWORE HE 'D GET ME BACK AND HERE WE ARE .
THIS PLACE WAS CALLED CROSSROADS MANUFACTURING
BEFORE IT CLOSED .
" LOOK BEYOND THE CROSSROADS ...
TO THE CLEAR DAWN . "
I DON 'T FOLLOW YOU .
THE MAN HE KILLED WAS RELEASED FROM CLEAR DAWN PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
WHEN THE STATE SHUT IT DOWN .
THAT BUILDING 'S BEEN ABANDONED FOR YEARS .
THAT 'S WHERE THE GAME IS BEING PLAYED .
ALL RIGHT , YOU GET BACK , YOU STAY WITH JILL TUCK .
DON 'T LET HER OUT OF YOUR SIGHT .
- Bobby . - JOYCE ?
Bobby . Bobby .
Bobby , I 'm here .
JOYCE .
Bobby , can you hear me ?
JOYCE , I CAN HEAR YOU . I CAN SEE YOU .
Bobby , I can see you too .
YES , BABY .
- GET ME OUT OF HERE . - Baby , I 'm on my way .
WHO 'S DOING THIS ? WHY ?
- Why is this happening ? - PLEASE , BABY , I 'M ON THE WAY .
- JUST HANG ON , OKAY ? - HURRY . PLEASE HURRY .
THERE 'S GOT TO BE A TAPE .
Hello , Bobby .
Before you is the door that leads to your wife .
However , you must first make a choice .
As you may have guessed , your decision will be as difficult
as pulling teeth .
The lock before you
requires a four-digit combination to open .
However , if it is access you seek ,
then a true sacrifice
will have to be made .
Watch and learn , Bobby .
The necessary numbers have been etched
onto two of your teeth .
Look to the chart as a reference
for which teeth to pull and in which order
to enter the digits .
Time is ticking down .
You must make your decision quickly .
Bobby !
I DON 'T WANT YOU TO SEE THIS , BABY , OKAY ?
OH MY GOD .
No . ( crying )
No .
LEFT SIDE CLEAR .
CLEAR .
- CLEAR . - CLEAR .
TAKE YOUR POSITIONS .
Gibson : THE GAME 'S STILL ON .
- ( cracking ) - ( grunting )
- LET 'S GO . - MOVE TO THE SECOND LEVEL .
- CLEAR . - CLEAR .
CLEAR .
GO .
( crunches )
( groaning )
- CLEAR UP . - ALL CLEAR .
MOVE MOVE .
- MOVING IN . - MOVING IN .
- CLEAR . - WE 'RE CLEAR .
( beeps )
( cell phone rings )
Officer : BLOCK IT OFF .
- What ? - I FOUND WHERE THAT MPEG CAME FROM .
- Where ? - A BUSINESS CALLED PETE 'S AUTO BODY ON 58th STREET .
- The junkyard . - THE LOCATION OF THE CAR TRAP .
YEAH , THAT 'S CORRECT .
- OKAY , YOU GUYS KEEP MOVING . - WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
- TO GET HOFFMAN . - OKAY , LET 'S MOVE IT .
( cell phone rings )
ROGERS .
- YEAH . - ( beeps )
WHAT ? WHAT HAPPENED ?
GIBSON 'S GOT HOFFMAN 'S LOCATION .
THE GAME ISN 'T OVER .
( grunting )
( crunches )
ANOTHER BODY .
- ( Bobby screaming ) - HOLD .
WE GOT A LIVE ONE .
CAN 'T CROSS HERE . LET 'S GO .
( beeps )
( siren wailing )
HEY , GO GET YOUR SHOTGUNS . YOU COME FOLLOW ME .
GIVE ME YOUR GUN .
Gibson : HOFFMAN , FREEZE .
I WANT YOU TO SLOWLY PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR .
- JOYCE . - BOBBY .
BOBBY , I KNEW YOU 'D MAKE IT .
- I KNEW YOU 'D FIND ME . - I AM SO SORRY .
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT . I KNEW YOU 'D COME .
GET ME OUT .
- ( electricity crackles ) - ( screams )
- BOBBY . OH MY GOD . - ( whimpering )
- THERE 'S GOTTA BE ANOTHER WAY . - ( static hisses )
( gasps )
Hello , Bobby .
You have almost completed your rebirth .
However , your final task
will be your most difficult .
The woman before you symbolizes your success .
She is your trophy .
And she has seen the good in your message ,
- despite its dishonest beginnings . - WHAT 'S HE TALKING ABOUT ?
Today , we will see
- if you can truly earn her love . - BOBBY .
To prove your status
as a survivor , you must overcome a game
that should be all too familiar .
- NO . - You supposedly survived it once already
so it should be easy to survive once again .
Pierce the hooks through your chest muscles ,
and the game will begin .
In order to free yourself and your wife ,
you must hoist yourself with these chains
and connect the extension cords above you
before the clock expires .
Both hands will be needed to complete this task .
But that should be simple .
For , as you claim to understand ,
the pectoral muscles can easily support your weight .
So I ask you , Bobby ,
when you embrace every day as if it is your last ,
will it be with your wife ?
Make your choice .
WHAT 'S HE TALKING ABOUT ?
BABY , I 'M SO SORRY .
I LIED .
I WAS NEVER IN A TRAP .
CLEAR .
( insects buzzing )
HOW COULD YOU LET ME BELIEVE THAT ?
I 'M GONNA MAKE THIS RIGHT .
YOU DON 'T DESERVE TO BE THERE .
I 'M YOUR WIFE .
HOW COULD YOU LIE TO ME ?
( crying )
HEY , I KNOW THAT FROM SOMEWHERE .
MAKE YOUR CHOICE . CLOCK 'S TICKING .
BAG THE OTHER BODIES . GET THEM BACK TO THE CORONER 'S OFFICE RIGHT AWAY .
Officer : WHAT IS THIS , SIR ?
HOFFMAN TAPPED INTO THE STATION 'S SECURITY SYSTEM .
HE 'S BEEN WATCHING US THE WHOLE TIME .
- ( beeps ) - ( explosion )
Gibson : OH MY GOD .
( cell phone beeps )
- ( phone rings ) - THIS IS PALMER .
LISTEN , YOU GET EVERY AVAILABLE OFFICER BACK TO THE STATION .
- I 'M SORRY , SIR ? - RIGHT NOW .
( rattling )
SIR .
GIBSON , ARE YOU STILL THERE ? GIBSON .
( gagging )
HEY , WHAT- - ?
- DOOR 'S LOCKED ! - WE 'RE LOCKED IN !
( gas hissing )
GAS ! GAS !
LOOK FOR AN EXIT .
( coughing )
I LOVE YOU , JOYCE .
I NEVER LIED ABOUT THAT .
I LOVE YOU .
BOBBY , I LOVE YOU .
- ( screaming ) - NO ! OH MY GOD .
( gasping )
NO .
GIBSON .
( muffled screaming )
( knife clatters )
( neck cracks )
YOU CAN DO IT . YOU CAN DO IT .
( screaming )
OH MY GOD .
BOBBY , I LOVE YOU .
YOU CAN DO IT .
HANG ON . HANG ON . HANG ON .
PULL . PULL , BOBBY . I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT .
PULL .
OH MY GOD . YOU CAN DO IT .
BOBBY , YOU CAN DO IT . OH MY GOD .
BOBBY !
PULL !
( knock on door )
( bangs )
- WHAT WAS THAT ? - THAT 'S IT , PULL . PULL !
- PULL . - ( grunting )
HURRY !
PULL . YOU 'RE ALMOST THERE .
FIGHT , BOBBY . YOU CAN DO IT .
SOMEONE 'S OUT THERE .
OH MY GOD . NO !
HELP ME ! HELP ME !
HELP ME ! NO !
I 'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU .
( panting )
( whimpers )
HOW DO I LOOK ?
( grunts )
BITCH .
HELP ME !
BOBBY , PLEASE , REACH .
GO .
BOBBY , REACH .
HURRY .
REACH . REACH !
YOU CAN DO IT , BOBBY .
( whimpering )
BOBBY , REACH . REACH .
ONE MORE . REACH . YOU CAN DO IT . BOBBY !
BOBBY , YOU CAN DO IT .
( screaming )
( screams ) BOBBY !
( groans )
NO !
BOBBY !
NO . BOBBY !
JOYCE !
( screaming ) BOBBY !
- JOYCE ! - BOBBY ! BOBBY !
( screaming )
JOYCE ! JOYCE !
( electricity crackling )
- BOBBY ! - ( sobbing )
( shouts )
YOU FUCKING CUNT .
- ( screaming ) - ( gasping )
NO ! BOBBY !
JOYCE !
NO !
BOBBY !
JOYCE !
- ( sizzling ) - ( sobbing )
- ( clicks ) - ( ticking )
( whimpering )
GAME OVER .
TV Announcer : Over the last two hours ,
it seems our entire city has been shaken to its core .
In addition to the nine police employees killed tonight ,
Jill Tuck , the wife of serial killer John Kramer , has been found dead .
- ( gas hissing ) - Citizens are being advised to report any activity
even remotely suspicious at this time
as blockades are being set up at major intersections
within a 30-mile radius
surrounding what will be considered the largest attack
on this city 's police department in our history .
Any citizens with information leading to the apprehension ...
( gasps )
WHAT THE FUCK ?
Jigsaw : Hello , Dr. Gordon .
You are perhaps my greatest asset .
CONGRATULATIONS , DR. GORDON . YOU SURVIVED .
( gasping )
Jigsaw : Without you , my work
over the last few years
would not have been possible .
( screams )
JEFF 'S WIFE ,
DR. LYNN DENLON .
SHE 'LL BE PERFECT .
MY EYES- - I CAN 'T SEE !
Jigsaw : That having been said , I have a request .
Watch over Jill .
And should anything happen to her ,
I want you to act immediately on my behalf .
In return for that ,
I will keep no more secrets from you .
I 've showed you a lot of places .
But there is one
that will be , perhaps , the most meaningful to you .
( screams )
( grunts )
( screaming )
I DON 'T THINK SO .
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU 'RE DOING ?
WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU THINK YOU 'RE DOING , HUH ?
NO .
YOU CAN 'T FUCKING DO THIS TO ME .
FUCK YOU . NO !
- GAME OVER . - NO !
( rock music playing )